<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
  <title>Josh Duncan – Blog</title>
  <atom:link href="https://joshbduncan.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <link>https://joshbduncan.com</link>
  <description>just some random thoughts published on the internet...</description>
  <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 16:43:03 EST</lastBuildDate>
  <language>en-US</language>

  
  <item>
    <title>Saving JSON &#34;like&#34; Preferences Files With Adobe ExtendScript</title>
    <link>https://joshbduncan.com/saving-preferences-in-adobe-extendscript.html</link>
    <description>Some of my scripts for Adobe products have the ability to save user preferences. Here&#39;s how I save those preferences to a JSON like file on disk using ExtendScript and the Adobe Bridge Messaging API.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>Progress Spinners Using Python Generators and Context Managers</title>
    <link>https://joshbduncan.com/python-progress-spinners-using-generators.html</link>
    <description>Making neat little progress spinners that let you know things are working in your cli apps is quite simple using Python generators and context manager.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>Search &amp; Filter HTML Table Data With JavaScript</title>
    <link>https://joshbduncan.com/search-and-filter-html-table-data-with-javascript.html</link>
    <description>Searching through HTML tables is super simple using  Vanilla JavaScript, a few query selectors, and some neat methods.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>Autofilling Two Factor Authentication (2FA) Codes in macOS Chrome</title>
    <link>https://joshbduncan.com/macos_chrome_autofill_security_codes.html</link>
    <description>If you use Chrome on macOS and are jealous of Safari&#39;s ability to autofill Two Factor Authentication (2FA) security codes checkout this sweet Keyboard Maestro macro.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>Custom Sorting in Python</title>
    <link>https://joshbduncan.com/python-custom-sorting.html</link>
    <description>I recently found myself needing to sort a list by cardinal directions. Here&#39;s a super simple solution to do custom sorting in Python.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>Checking off Linked Records in an Airtable Script</title>
    <link>https://joshbduncan.com/checking-linked-records-in-airtable.html</link>
    <description>I needed a quick way to check off a bunch of linked records in Airtable so I worked up this little script to do it from an Airtable button.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>JavaScript Search Token Highlighter</title>
    <link>https://joshbduncan.com/javascript-search-token-highlighter.html</link>
    <description>Building a search results page? Thinking about highlighting the search terms so they standout? Here&#39;s how I did it using vanilla JavaScript.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>Trying Out Things 3</title>
    <link>https://joshbduncan.com/trying-out-things-3.html</link>
    <description>I decided to switch my to-do list to Things 3 and needed to move a lot of to-dos over from Todoist. Seemed like a great project to explore their API and save myself a bunch of copying and pasting.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>Python Type Hints and Fancy Banners</title>
    <link>https://joshbduncan.com/python-type-hints-and-banners.html</link>
    <description>While leaning about Python Type Hints, I wrote a nifty little function to display cool banners and help remind me about the concepts of type hinting.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>RSS Feeds Using Flask-FlatPages</title>
    <link>https://joshbduncan.com/flask-flatpages-rss.html</link>
    <description>Need to generate a valid RSS feed for your Flask website? Using Flask-FlatPages? Well, it&#39;s really quite simple.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>Generating a Sitemap with Flask and Flask-FlatPages</title>
    <link>https://joshbduncan.com/flask-flatpages-sitemap.html</link>
    <description>If you&#39;re using Flask-FlatPages, it&#39;s really simple to generate a sitemap that plays nice with search engines and helps your website get noticed.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>Unpacking Tuples in a For Loop</title>
    <link>https://joshbduncan.com/unpacking-tuples-in-a-for-loop.html</link>
    <description>Have you ever noticed as you learn more and more of a programming language, you often forgo the basics for a more complex solution? Well, today I was reminded of the KISS principle when I needed to unpack a bunch of tuples.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
  </item>
  

</channel>
</rss>